{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "How many people have climbed to the summit of Everest?",
      "answers": [
        "2000",
        "10",
        "2000",
        "5454",
        0,
        "2000",
        "4000"
      ],
      "average": 1910.6666666666667,
      "correctAnswer": 4000
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "How many billionaires are there in the world (as of 2019)?",
      "answers": [
        0,
        "5000",
        "3000",
        0,
        "300"
      ],
      "average": 2000,
      "correctAnswer": 2153
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "How many years does it take a space-shuttle to get to Mars?",
      "answers": [
        "4000",
        "150",
        0,
        "140"
      ],
      "average": 1383.3333333333333,
      "correctAnswer": 150
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What is the hottest temperature (degrees celsius) ever recorded on earth?",
      "answers": [
        "60",
        "60"
      ],
      "average": 60,
      "correctAnswer": 57
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "How many days can you go without water?",
      "answers": [
        "4",
        "5"
      ],
      "average": 4,
      "correctAnswer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "How many calories in a banana?",
      "answers": [
        "100",
        "100"
      ],
      "average": 100,
      "correctAnswer": 89
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "How long do cats live for?",
      "answers": [
        "15",
        "12"
      ],
      "average": 15,
      "correctAnswer": 89
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "How many times does ireland fit into australia?",
      "answers": [
        "50",
        "200"
      ],
      "average": 50,
      "correctAnswer": 110
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "How many countries in the world?",
      "answers": [
        "190",
        "120",
        "250",
        "50",
        "200",
        "100"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 195,
      "average": 162
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "how many people have walked on the moon?",
      "answers": [
        "15",
        "5",
        "5"
      ],
      "average": 10,
      "correctAnswer": 13
    }
  ]
}